罗斯吻了我      不会吧
Ross kissed me.         No!
我的天啊 我的天啊 我的天啊
Oh my God! Oh my God! Oh my God!
太不可思议了
It was unbelievable!
我的天啊 我的天啊 我的天啊
Oh my God! Oh my God! Oh my God！
我们要听整个经过
Okay, all right. We wanna hear everything.
摩妮卡 去拿酒 拔掉电话线
Monica, get the wine and unplug the phone.
好
Okay.
瑞秋 结局好不好 我们需不需要纸巾
Rachel, does this end well or do we need to get tissues?
结局非常好      噢
Oh, it ended very well.         Oh.
等我来了再开始 等我来了再开始
Do not start without me! Do not start without me!
先说说那个吻
Okay. All right. Let's hear about the kiss.
是像 拂过你嘴唇的轻吻呢
Was it like, was it like a soft brush against your lips.
还是像 "我现在就要你" 的那种吻呢
Or was it like a, you know, "I gotta have you now" kind of thing?
刚开始很热烈 然后
Well, at first it was really intense, you know? And then...
天啊 后来我们就沉醉在里面了
Oh God! And then we just sort of sunk into it.
他是抱着你的吗
Oh! So, okay, was he holding you?
还是把手放在你背后
Or were his hands like on your back?
不 事实上 刚开始他的手放在我的腰上
No, actually, first they started out on my waist.
然后游移上来 到我的头发
And then they slid up and then they were in my hair.
后来我吻了她      舌吻
And, and then I kissed her.        Tongue?
没错      太酷了
Yeah.         Cool.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第08集
清单  The One With the List
调校制作：海盗美剧 寒 枫
字幕编辑：海盗美剧 小龟快快跑
好了 看看这个坏小子
All right, check out this bad boy!
12MB内存 500MB硬盘
Twelve megabytes of RAM, five hundred megabyte hard drive,
内置电子数据表格功能
builtin spreadsheet capabilities,
再加上一个 速率为28Kbps的调制解调器
and a modem that transmits at over 28000BPS.
哇 你要用它来做什么
Wow! What are you gonna use it for?
打电玩之类的
Games and stuff.
没工作 没有适合我的工作
There are no jobs. There are no jobs for me.
喔 等等 这里有一个
Oh, wait, here's one.
你愿意裸体煮菜吗
Would you be willing to cook naked?
有人要找裸体厨师吗
There's an ad for a naked chef?
不是 但如果你愿意裸体煮菜
No, but if you're willing to cook naked,
那或许就能裸体跳舞
then you might be willing to dance naked.
然后就
And then...
嘿      嘿
Hey!        Hey！
对了 你昨晚亲热得怎么样
Oh, so how'd you make out last night?
很风趣 痛苦的风趣 不 等等
That is funny. That is painfully funny. No, wait, wait.
没错 就只是痛苦而已
Yeah, that's just painful.
等等 我以为昨晚很愉快
Wait a minute. I thought last night was great.
对 没错 但当我到回家
Yeah, it was. But I get home, okay.
看到茱莉放在我床头柜上的盐水
And I see Julie's saline solution on my night table.
我就想 天啊 我这是在干什么
And I'm thinking to myself, "Oh my God! What the hell am I doing?"
我跟茱莉这么好的女人在一起
I mean, here I am with Julie, this incredible great woman,
我喜欢她 她也喜欢我
who I care about and who cares about me.
难不成我就这样 把这一切都抛掉吗
and I'm like, what, am I just gonna throw all that away?
一瓶盐水 就给你这么大的启示
You got all that from saline solution?
等等 我们现在谈的是瑞秋
Wait a minute. We're talking about Rachel here.
你跟瑞秋的事
You and Rachel.
相信我 我梦想能跟瑞秋在一起 想了有十年了
Believe me, I've been dreaming about me and Rachel for like ten years now.
但现在我跟茱莉在一起
But now I'm with Julie.
就好像 到底是我跟茱莉 还是我跟瑞秋
You know? So it's like, me and Julie, me and Rachel.
我跟茱莉 我跟瑞秋
Me and Julie, me and Rach.
瑞秋 瑞秋
Rachel! Rachel!
嘿 你好      你好吗
Hey, you.         How are you?
很好 你呢      很好
Good. How are you?         Good.
嗨 亲爱的      嗨 茱莉 茱莉
Hi, honey.         Hi, Julie. Hi, Julie?
茱莉
Julie!
你好吗
How are you?
很好      很好
Good.        Good.
这么说 大家都在这儿
So every body's here.
大家都很好
Everybody's good.
你要弹点什么吗 菲比
So, were you gonna play something, Phoebe?
事实上      弹吧
Oh. Well, actually...        Play it!
好吧
All right.
茱莉 我不知道你戴隐形眼镜      什么
Julie, I didn't know you wore lenses.         What?
好的 各位好
Okay. Hi.
各位好 可以了
Hello. Hi. Okay.
这是一首关于三角恋爱的歌
So, this is a song about a love triangle
发生在我虚构的三个人物之间
between three people that I made up.
歌名是 "其中两人昨晚接吻了"
It's called, "Two of Them Kissed Last Night."
有个女孩名叫贝蒂
There was a girl we'll call her Betty.
还有个男孩名叫尼尔
And a guy let's call him Neil.
我想特别郑重声明
Now I can't stress this point too strongly.
这故事不是真的
This story isn't real
现在尼尔必须决定
Now our Neil must decide.
他要放弃哪个女孩
Who will be the girl that he casts aside?
是他深爱的那个贝蒂
Will Betty be the one who he loves truly?
还是那个叫露俐的女孩
Or will it be the one who we'll call Loolie?
他必须决定 他必须决定
He must decide. He must decide.
虽然他纯属虚构 但他必须决定
Even though I made him up, he must decide.
这履历写得很好 很好 很好
This is a nice resume. Nice, nice, nice.
非常令人印象深刻
Muy impressivo.
莱斯特先生 这工作具体是要做什么
So, Mr. Rastatter, what exactly does this job entail?
广告里没说清楚
The ad wasn't too clear.
摩克力      什么
Mockolate.        I'm sorry?
摩克力 这是一种完全人造的巧克力的替代产品
Mockolate. It's a synthetic chocolate substitute.
别客气 试一块
Well, go ahead, try a piece.
我们认为摩克力比巧克力更好吃
Yeah, we think that Mockolate is even better than chocolate.
好的
All right.
对吧
Yeah.
我喜欢它碎掉的感觉
I love how it crumbles.
那是巧克力不会有的
You see, chocolate doesn't do that.
我们很快就能得到食品认证
Anyhoo, we should be getting our FDA approval any day now.
希望能在感恩节前上市
Hopefully, in time for Thanksgiving.
在我们看来 巧克力已经占据了
See, the way we look at it, chocolate already dominates
几个要吃大餐的节日 复活节 圣诞节等
your major food preparation holidays, Easter, Christmas, what have you.
但我们相信 只要有适当的市场营销
But we're thinking given the right marketing,
我们可以把感恩节变成摩克力的节日
we can make Thanksgiving the Mockolate holiday.
哇
Wow.
你不吞下去吗
Do you wanna swallow that?
我在等泡泡消失
Just waiting for it to stop bubbling.
是啊 那很棒对吧
Yeah. Isn't that great?
总之 我们想找几个大厨
Well, anyhoo, we are looking for a couple of chefs,
创作出一些感恩节主题的食谱
who can create some Thanksgiving themed recipes.
你有兴趣吗
You think you might be interested?
绝对 有
Abso... lutely!
我喜欢创作食谱
See, I love creating new recipes.
也喜欢感恩节 现在我还爱上了摩克力
I love Thanksgiving. And well, now I love Mockolate.
真的
Really?
尤其是那余味 我敢说
Especially that aftertaste. You know, I tell you,
可以撑到圣诞节
that'll last you till Christmas.
摩克力慕思如何
How about Mockolate mousse?
感觉不像感恩节的味道
It's not, it's not very Thanksgiving-y.
那么清教徒摩克力慕思呢
Okay, how about Pilgrim Mockolate mousse?
要怎么跟清教徒扯上关系
What makes it Pilgrim?
放些金属扣在上面
We'll put buckles on it.
嘿     嘿      嘿
Hey.         Hey.        Hey.
罗斯来电话没      对不起 没有
Did Ross call?         No, I'm sorry.
他为什么不打
Why didn't he call?
他要跟茱莉在一起 对吧
He's gonna stay with Julie, isn't he?
他会选择她
He's gonna stay with her.
而她会说
And she's gonna be all,
嗨 我是茱莉 罗斯选择了我
Hi, I'm Julie. Ross picked me.
我们会结婚生子
And we're gonna to get married, have a lot of kids.
一起老死
And dig up stuff together!
无意冒犯 但听起来一点都不像她
No offense, but that sounds nothing like her.
我不知道该怎么办 我该怎么办
I don't know what am I gonna do. What am I gonna do?
这简直就是个恶梦
I mean, this, this is like a complete nightmare.
我知道 这一定很难
Oh, I know. This must be so hard.
不要啊 有两个女人爱我
Oh no! Two women love me!
她们两个都漂亮又性感
They're both gorgeous and sexy.
我的钱包太小 装不下这些50块的纸币
My wallet's too small for my 50s.
我的钻石鞋也太紧了
And my diamond shoes are too tight!
我想到了 罗斯
Hey, here's a thought, Ross...
别碰电脑 永远别碰
Don't touch the computer. Don't ever touch the computer.
罗斯 送你三个字
Ross, listen, I got two words for you:
三人行
Threesome.
好 我们理性一点
Ok, all right, look. Let's get logical about this, okay?
我们列张单子 写出瑞秋和茱莉的优缺点
We'll make a list. Rachel and Julie, pros and cons.
名字可以用不同字体的粗体字
We'll put their names in bold with different fonts.
然后每一栏 可以用不同的颜色来写
And I can use different colors for each column.
不能用笔写的吗      不行 你个土老冒儿
Can't we just use a pen?         No, Amish boy.
我们先从缺点开始 那样比较好玩
All right, let's start with the cons because they're more fun.
先说瑞秋吧
Rachel first.
不知道 我是说
I don't know. I mean...
好吧 我想你可以说 她有时候有一点被宠坏了
All right, I guess you can say she's a little spoiled sometimes.
没有错
You could say that.
有时候她还有点没脑子
I guess, you know, sometimes she's a little ditzy, you know?
有时候她也太注重外表了
And I've seen her be a little too into her looks.
茱莉和我有很多共同点
Oh, and Julie and I have a lot in common.
因为我们都是古生物学家
Because we're both paleontologists, right?
瑞秋只是个服务生
But Rachel's just a waitress.
服务生
Waitress.
了解 你们想玩《毁灭战士》吗
Got it. You guys wanna play "Doom"?
我们也可以继续写
Or we could keep doing this.
还有什么
What else?
我不知道
I don't know.
噢 她的脚踝有点肉肉的
Oh, her ankles are a little chubby.
好吧 说说茱莉吧 她有什么不好
Okay, let's do Julie. What's wrong with her?
她不是瑞秋
She's not Rachel.
好 这是摩克力酥皮南瓜派
Okay. This is pumpkin pie with a Mockolate crust.
这是摩克力蔓越莓蛋糕 那是碎摩克力饼干
This is Mockolate cranberry cake, and these are Mockolatechip cookies.
就像当初印地安人做的那样
Just like the Indians served.
哦天啊      是好吃的意思吗
Oh my God!         "Oh my God" good?
哦天啊 我不敢相信 你让我吃这种东西
Oh my God! I can't believe you let me put this in my mouth.
老天爷 这一定就是万恶之味
Oh! Oh sweet Lord! This is what evil must taste like!
我告诉你 这个玩意儿不能打印
I'm telling you, this thing won't print.
是的 那个按钮 我都按了一百回了
Yes, I pressed that button like a hundred times.
你一点都不热情 这算哪门子的热线电话
You know, for a hotline, you're not so hot.
那是什么声音
What is that in the background?
你是在看"星际迷航"吗
Are you watching "Star Trek"?
嘿
Hey.
你跟茱莉怎么样 她很伤心吗
So how'd it go with Julie? Did you break her heart?
是啊 场面很糟糕
Yes. It was horrible.
她哭了 我也哭了 她扔东西 砸到我
She cried. I cried. She threw things, they hit me.
我做了正确的事
I did the right thing.
那么 史波克真的拥抱了他的父亲
So, Spock actually hugs his father?
嘿 你们有
Hey, do you guys have...
嗨      嗨
Hi!        Hi!
你要去哪儿
Where're you going?
我刚回来
I just got back from...
从茱莉那儿
From Julie's.
不 不是你想的那样
No, no. It's not what you think.
是别的事
It's the other thing.
什么别的事 我想的是什么
Well, what's the other thing? What do I think?
这个嘛
Well.
他跟茱莉分手了
He broke up with Julie!
快去抱她 看在老天的份上
Well, go hug her, for God's sakes!
是真的      真的
Really?        Really.
我爱的一直是你 瑞秋      噢 天啊
It's always been you, Rach.        Oh, God！
噢 这太好了 真是太好了
Oh, this is good.  This is really good.
我知道 我几乎
I know I know. It's, it's almost...
我们出去走走好吗 就我们俩 不跟他们
What do you say, we go take a walk? Just us. Not them.
好的 我去拿外套
Okay. Let me get my coat.
好的 不 嘿 等等
Okay. No, hey, whoa, whoa.
我去帮你拿      好
I'll get your coat.        Okay!
他去帮我拿外套  他去帮我拿外套 乔伊
He's going to get my coat. He's going to get my coat, Joey!
我的天啊 我真不敢相信 真是太棒了
Oh my God, you guys, I can't believe this! This is unbelievable!
这是什么      什么 没什么
What's that?         What? Nothing!
我看到我的名字了 那是什么      没有 你看
What? I saw my name. What is it?         No no see? See?
嘿 能打印了
Hey, it's printing!
嘿 打出来了
那是什么 让我看看
What is it? Let me see!
有人订外套吗
Hey, someone order a coat?
罗斯 钱德在他的电脑上 写了关于我的东西
Ross, Chandler wrote something about me on his computer.
而且还不让我看
And he won't let me see.
他不让你看 他不让你看
He won't? He won't!
因为那是你写的短篇小说
Because isn't that the short story you were writing?
是的 这是我写的短篇小说
Yes, it is a short story that I was writing.
里面有我吗 那让我看看
And I'm in it? Then let me read it.
不行
No!
拜托
Come on!
嘿 要不你念给她听
Hey, why don't you read it to her?
好吧
All right.
那是个夏天
It was summer.
天气很热
And it was hot.
瑞秋在那里
Rachel was there.
一张寂寞的灰沙发
A lonely gray couch.
尼德大叫 "哦 快看"
"Oh, look!" cried Ned.
然后他就永远的当上了国王 完
And then the kingdom was his forever. The end.
就这样 你就写了这些
That's it? That's all you wrote?
你是全世界最烂的作家
You're the worst writer in the whole world!
好了 我不觉得好玩了
All right, you know what? This isn't funny anymore.
那纸上一定写了我关于我的什么 我要看
There's something about me on that piece of paper, and I want to see it.
不 不行
No, you don't.
好吧 算了
All right, you know what, that's fine.
你们要是这么幼稚的话 那就算了
If you guys want to be children about this, that's fine.
我不要看了
I do not need to see it.
这是什么      那是
What is this?          That is...
罗斯 这是什么
Ross, what is this?
谢了      祝你好运
Thank you.       Good luck.
好吧 你只要记住 我有多爱你就行了 好吗
Okay. Just remember how crazy I am about you, okay?
有点没脑子 太注重外表 被宠坏了
"Kind of ditzy"? "Too into her looks"? "Spoiled"?
是 有一点被宠坏了
No, that's a little spoiled.
那个白痴 少打了 有一点
He was supposed to type "little", the idiot!
只是个服务生
"Just a waitress"?
那是
Now, that was,
我是说 相对于
I mean, as opposed to,
好吧 你饶了我吧 瑞秋
The... Okay, is this over yet? Rach?
我的脚踝没有肉肉的
I do not have chubby ankles!
不 等等  好吧 好吧 看另一边
No, no, wait, okay, okay, okay, look at the other side.
看茱莉的那一栏
Look at Julie's column.
她不是瑞球
She's not Rachem?
不是       瑞球是什么东西
No.        What the hell's a Rachem?
不是 不是
No, no.
是古生物学家会用的愚蠢字眼
Is that some stupid paleontology word
而我没听过 因为我只是个服务生
that I wouldn't know because I'm just a waitress?
瑞秋 别这样 瑞秋 瑞秋
No. Rach, come on! Rach! Rach!
瑞秋 不是的
Rach! No, no!
那写的是 "她不是瑞秋" 她不是
It's "She's not Rachel"! She's not...
瑞秋
Rachel?
我的日记 我的日记 太聪明了
My diary. My diary! That's brilliant!
如果我说 是我的日记的话
I should have told her it was my diary.
她就不会要我念了
She never would have made me read her my diary.
那倒是真的
No, that's true.
你是很好的事后诸葛
You know, you'd be a great person to have around the day after an emergency.
我不敢相信罗斯会列这种清单
I cannot believe Ross even made this list.
就是说啊      真是个白痴
I know.         What a dinkus!
别再骂他了 那是钱德的主意
Hey, cut him some slack. It was Chandler's idea.
什么      什么
What?         What?
很好 我就是在等这一刻
Oh, good. I was hoping that would come up.
那是你的主意
This was your idea?
好吧 我们凭心而论 好不好
All right, let's get some perspective here, okay?
事出必有因
These things happen for a reason.
是啊 就是你
Yeah. You!
菲比 帮我一下 好不好
All right, Pheebs, back me up here. Okay?
你信因果轮回之类的鬼话 是不是
You believe in that karma crap, don't you?
是啊 顺便祝你 下辈子当屎壳郎 生活幸福
Yeah, by the way, good luck in your next life as a dung beetle.
瑞秋
Rach!
打开 好吗
Hey! Open up! Please?
罗斯 当你按门铃 别人不让你进
When somebody does not buzz you in, Ross,
那就是说 让你滚蛋
that means "Go away".
而不是叫你爬消防梯上来
That doesn't mean "Climb up the firee scape".
我只是想念给你听 你的优点
I just want to read you something, it's your "Pro List".
没兴趣
Not interested.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
第一 你看游戏节目时会哭
Number one, the way you cry at game shows.
第二 你很爱你的朋友
Number two, how much you love your friends.
第三 你紧张时会玩头发
Number three, the way you play with your hair when you're nervous.
第四 你能勇敢地开始你的新生活
Number four, how brave you are for starting your life over.
第五 你对小本很好
Number five, how great you are with Ben.
第六 你的香味
Number six, the way you smell.
嘿 罗斯 你在干嘛
Hey, Ross, what are you doing?
嘿 乔伊 打开窗子 好不好
Hey, Joey, you wanna open the window?
当然
Oh, yeah.
你在外面干嘛      我
What are you doing out there?         I'm...
我的天 你一定冻坏了 你知道你需要什么吗
My gosh, you must be freezing. You know what you need?
来杯热腾腾的摩克力如何
How about a nice steaming cup of hot Mockolate?
瑞秋 拜托 开门
Rach, come on, open up.
瑞秋 拜托 你得再给我一次机会
Rach, come on. Come on. You gotta give me another chance.
不要
No.
不要      没有错
No?         That's what I said.
也许我们该离开一下
Maybe we should go.
不 不需要 我们讲完了
No, you guys, you really don't have to go, we're done talking.
瑞秋 我知道 你肯定
Rach, come on. I know how you must......
不 你不知道 罗斯
No, you don't, Ross.
想像你自己最糟糕的缺点
Imagine the worst things you think about yourself.
如果换是你 当这个世界上你最信任的人
Now, how would you feel if the one person that you trusted the most in the world,
不仅也这样认为
not only thinks them too,
还把它们当作不跟你在一起的原因 你有什么感受
but actually uses them as reasons not to be with you.
但我想跟你在一起 尽管你有那些缺点
No, but, but see, I wanna be with you in spite of all those things.
你还真伟大 罗斯 我说了 不准走
Oh well, that's mighty big of you, Ross. I said, don't go!
你知道吗 你知道吗
You know what? You know what?
如果今天我们调换
If things were the other way around,
由你来列出我的缺点
there was nothing you could put on a list,
不管我感觉如何受伤 都不会让我 不想跟你在一起
that would ever make me not wanna be with you.
我猜那就是我们之间的差异
Well, then I guess that's the difference between us.
我是绝对不会列清单的
See, I'd never make a list.
我总是不懂遇到这种情况
I never know how long you're supposed to wait
要等多久才能再开口说话
in this type of situation before you can talk again.
或许再等一会儿
Maybe a little longer.
这其中的一些食谱
Now, in some of these recipes,
用量可能不太寻常
the quantities may seem just a little unusual.
比如说椰子摩克力坚果棒
like these coconut Mockolate holiday nut bars,
我用四杯椰子粉和四杯碎坚果
I've indicated four cups of coconut and four cups of crushed nuts,
但只有一汤匙摩克力
and only one table spoon of Mockolate.
无所谓了      什么
Doesn't matter.        What?
我们的食品认证没有下来
Our FDA approval didn't come through.
实验室老鼠出了问题
Something about laboratory rats.
天哪 我很遗憾
Oh gosh! I'm sorry.
是啊 不过 这是你的支票
Yeah, well, anyhoo, here is your check.
感谢你这么费心准备
Thank you for all the trouble you went through.
你在准备食谱时 没吃太多摩克力吧
Listen, you didn't eat a lot of it while you were cooking, did you?
我是吃了一些
Well, I ate some.
哦 一些 那没关系 没有很多就好
Oh, some. That's fine. Some's fine. Some's not a lot.
你尿尿时没有灼热感吧
So it doesn't burn when you pee, does it?
喂
Hello.
嗨
Hi!
又是他吗
Is that him again?
告诉他 我本想去接电话
Tell him I'd come to the phone,
但我的脚踝太重了 我走不动
but my ankles are weighing me down.
我想现在时机不对
Listen, I don't think this is the best time.
你能帮我一个忙吗
Look, can you do something for me?
可以啊 做什么
Sure. What?
好的
Okay.
可以
Alll right.
听音乐好吗
Music?
好啊      好的
Sure.         Okay.
下一首是 罗斯要送给瑞秋的歌曲
The next one's dedicated to Rachel from Ross.
瑞秋 他想告诉你 他深感抱歉
Rachel, he wants you to know he's deeply sorry for what he did.
他希望你能够原谅他
And he hopes you can find it in your heart to forgive him.
看到你眼若冰霜
See the stones set in your eyes.
看到你浑身带刺
See the thorn twist in your side,
我会等你的
I'll wait for you.
上天实在作弄人
Sleight of hand and twist of fate.
她就让我苦苦的等
On a bed of nails she makes me wait.
不论你是否在身旁 我会等的
And I'll wait without you.
我们刚接到瑞秋来电
We've just gotten a call from Rachel.
她告诉我们罗斯的恶行
And she told us what Ross did.
那真是令人发指 罗斯 如果你在听的话
It's pretty appalling. And, Ross, if you're listening,
我不想再播你的歌了
I don't wanna play your song anymore.
我们还是把时间 花在有希望的情侣身上
Why don't we devote our time to a couple that stands a chance?
艾佛瑞 蜜雪儿很抱歉用车撞你
Avery, Michelle's sorry she hit you with her car.
她希望你们俩能够和好
And she hopes you two will work it out.
我有一个房间 可以让你诉说心中的秘密
There's a room where I can go and tell my secrets to.
在我的房间里
In my room.
嗨 谢谢你再度过来
Hi. Thanks for coming in again.
不客气 我没有良心 而且我需要现金
Oh, not at all. I have no morals, and I need the cash.
我好像在照镜子
It's like I'm looking in a mirror.
言归正传 这东西叫开心鱼
Anyway, they're called Fishtachios.
吃起来完全像开心果
Now, they taste exactly like pistachios.
但主要是用鱼肉重新压制的
But they're made primarily of reconstituted fish bits.
来吧 尝尝看      好吧
Here, try one.        All right.
你有什么过敏问题吗      猫毛
You're not allergic to anything?        Cat hair.
喔 对不起
Oh, sorry.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧